<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prince Namwali</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prince Namwali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Extended Definition 📚</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/extended_definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/extended_definition/</guid>
      <description>The motto for Urban Dictionary is &amp;ldquo;Define Your World&amp;rdquo;, but thats probably offensive to Etymologists. Language is a living and breathing thing, its only natural that words change meaning over time, evolve or eventullay die out in usage. I find myself fascinated by words, not at the level of an etymologist or a sapiosexual, but at the polyglot level, i probably just made that up. I claim to have a deeper understanding of some words which i have interpreted using some twisted logic and this is a list of those words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mater Artium Necessitas 🚀</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/uvumbuzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/uvumbuzi/</guid>
      <description>Necessity is the mother of invention, but it all starts with a question. Is this the only way? What do i need that the currently available options don&amp;rsquo;t provide? How can we change this? Why? How come? Is there a better way? How can this be improved? What if? And the list of questions goes on and on.
Necessity is behind why we search for information on the internet. You could be looking for the definition of a word, a code solution on stack overflow, more information about a person or just about anything you are curious about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year: Second Brain 🧠</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2021-reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2021-reboot/</guid>
      <description>I started the year 2021 with a bang. I learned about this awesome personal knowledge management system called a Second Brain. The Second Brain is a digital note taking system that was invented by Tiago Forte and it has multiple great benefits, one of them being a solution to information overload. I was immediately intrigued just by the wording alone and i was able to find even more information by digging through YouTube and their official podcast, Building A Second Brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sayonara 2020 💔</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2020/</guid>
      <description>2020 marked the year, when all humanity was connected and forced to change. Everyone has a story to tell as a result of it and here is mine&amp;hellip; For the first time in my life, i experienced what its like to have your plans not work out, as if that has never happened before. Maybe it was different this time or maybe it was the same as an infant learning to walk, but constantly being greeted by the gravitational pull of failure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>


