<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Second Brain</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Second Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2021 Prince Kaizen Namwali</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Frugal Vtubing</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/vtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/vtube/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll present to you a very efficient way to Vtube using your Android device, scrcpy, REALITY App and OBS Studio.
This is our goal (click on the image to see its full resolution):

-- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethereal Sleep</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/sleep/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t pinpoint the exact date, but I was listening to Gregorian Chants, while working on something. In the heat of the moment, I though to myself, &amp;lsquo;this would pretty cool with some rain sounds in the background.&amp;rsquo; I should have just dismissed the thought then, but my curiosity got the best of me. The next steps were visibly clear, I simply needed to download the soundtracks and combine them with Audacity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Navigation</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/nav/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/nav/</guid>
      <description>Comfort and Laziness have been my longest business partners, since the dawn of time. This site looks empty because Hugo is generous enough to have a draft = true Front Matter. In the meantime, I made some super cool placeholder titles and I&amp;rsquo;ll leave you with this awesome art manifesto by Austin Kleon -
Draw the art you want to see, start the business you want to run, play the music you want to hear, write the books you want to read, build the products you want to use – do the work you want to see done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>My Setup &amp;amp; Tools  OS 💻: Artix Linux + AwesomeWM  Engine 🎮 : Godot Editor 🖥️: Neovim + Spacevim &amp;amp; Onivim 2 Langs ❤️: Go, GDScript, Lua, Bash Art 🔥: Inkscape, Gimp, Aseprite, DAW : Reaper Second Brain 🧠: Obsidian Foam &amp;amp; Markor Tech 🚀: Hugo, Browser 🌍: EinkBro, Privacy Browser &amp;amp;, Qutebrowser LibreWolf Wallet ₿: Metamask &amp;amp; Monero CLI Addons:: uBlock Origin, Dark Reader, IPFS Companion, Lighthouse, Leechblock NG, NoScript, uMatrix, Vim Vixen  Digital Footprint  Github  Audius Dribbble LMMS BitDegree Creary LBRY Rive  Pixabay  Welcome to my Blog!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
