<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Second Brain</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Second Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2021 Prince Namwali</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Digital Minimalism with T-UI Launcher  </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/tui/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/tui/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i am going to talk about one of my favorite android launchers, T-UI launcher. Its the fastest and smallest launcher on android, but not many people may not about it. The guiding questions for this post include:
 What makes T-UI launcher special? Who is T-UI launcher for? What are some things you can do with T-UI launcher? How much battery do you save when using T-UI launcher?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Extraordinary power of mind mapping </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/mindmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/mindmap/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i talk about the most shocking revelation i encountered as i was learning and using mindmaps. Its possible to summarize a book with a mind map without having to read it and better yet, just by glancing at the table of contents. The guiding questions for this post shall be as follows:
 What is a mindmap? What are the different types of mind maps? Which mindmap style is the most useful?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Isekai &amp; Maladaptive Daydreaming </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/isekai/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/isekai/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i try to draw the correlation between 2 unrelated terms whose characteristic are much more similar than they are apart. The guiding questions for this post include:
 What is Isekai? What is Maladaptive Daydreaming? What are the differences between Isekai and Maladaptive daydreaming? What are the similarities between Isekai and Maladaptive daydreaming? How can Isekai influence Maladaptive Daydreaming?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Composing Procedurally Generated Music </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/procgen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/procgen/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i talk about how anyone can create music. You dont need any music theory, proprietary software or fancy hardware. The only requirement is your sense of hearing. The questions that will guide me through the thought process include?
 What is procedural generation? (general term) What is procedurally generated music? What tools can i use? Is procgen cheating? Why is procgen peak efficiency as opposed to laziness?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gelotology and NLP</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/gelotology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/gelotology/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i talk about the correlation between stand up comedy and neuro linguistic programming(NLP). The guiding questiong include:
 What is gelotology? What is Neuro Linguistic Programming? What does comedy have to do with NLP? What are some examples of NLP is comedy? Why is Bill Burr a perfect example of NLP in action? Where does self deprecating humor fall into this?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manhwa &amp; Manga Can Enhance Your Writing </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/manhwa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/manhwa/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i talk about how Manga and Manhwa can enhance your writing. This post assumes you are already familiar with those terms,but just a quick recap - Japanese comics are called Manga, Korean comics are called Manhwa and Chinese comics are Manhua. The guiding questions for this post include?
 How exactly does reading these particular comics help with writing? We think in pictures, but we speak in words, what does that have to do with anything?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sapien Isolation</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/isolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/isolation/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i simply document the events that happened since the inception of Covid-19. This post is simply a collection of information form various data points. It can be used by the reader or writer to write or expand upon these topics. The list will keep expanding and i&amp;rsquo;ll update every once in a while. You can use this to your advantage to write a well polished book,blog post or essay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Vim as Second Brain </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/vim/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/vim/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post i am going to challenge myself and try to see, if its possible to use vim as a Second Brain. The questions that will guide me through the process are as follows:
 How can you preview markdown files in Vim? How do you link your notes in Vim? What plugins are useful? How many plugins do you need? Which vim distribution has all the features you are looking for out the box?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mater Artium Necessitas 🚀</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/uvumbuzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/uvumbuzi/</guid>
      <description>Mater artium necessitas is a quote by Plato that was translated by a theologian by the name Benjamin Jowett, which means necessity is the mother of invention Throughout my encounter with this english proverb I have found that almost all instances of it have one thing in common. I would humbly extend the quote by saying necessity is the mother of invention, but it all starts with a question .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Navigation</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/nav/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/nav/</guid>
      <description>Write what you want to read   Mater Artium Necessitas 🚀  Neocolonial Nyasaland  Thokozani; A Story About Gratitude  Bye Bye Plutonomy, Welcome Freedom!  Extended Definition 📚  Afropolitan Excellence  Q&amp;amp;A ( ͡👁️ ͜ʖ ͡👁️)  The Death of Academia  New Year; Second Brain 🧠  Sayonara 2020 💔  Using Vim as a Second Brai  Unlimited Creativity; How to compose procedurally generated music  Deciphering comedy using Neuro Linguistic Programming  Why Reading Manga &amp;amp; Manhwa can enhance your writing  Isekai and Maladaptive Daydreaming  The Power of Mind Mapping; Summarizing books without reading  Digital Minimalism with T-UI Launcher  The Power of Questions and Rational Emotive Behavior Therapy (coming soon)  The Duopoly of the Comical West; Marvel &amp;amp; DC (coming soon)  Government; The Monopoly of Life (coming soon)  Human Languages and the Modern Day Polyglot (coming soon)  Technological Overkill; Using Blender to Animate SVG&amp;rsquo;s (coming soon)  Symbiotic Nature of Humans and Machines (coming soon)  Practical Gamification for non game developers (coming soon)  Zettlekasten vs The Second Brain (coming soon)  Unlocking Gratitude with a Second Brain (coming soon)  Transient Hypofrontality Addiction (coming soon)  Choir; The Gateway to Annunication and Accent Transformation (coming soon)  Manhua; A Medium of Indoctrination (coming soon)  Uncanny Transformation; Intriguing Career Shifts (coming soon)  Modular Synthesis; The Ultimate Form of Procedurally Generated Music (coming soon)  The Eagle From Dagestan and the Last Stylebender (coming soon)  The Dichotomy of Conspiracy Theories and Revisionist History (coming soon)  Using a Game Engine to Make Music Videos (coming soon)  The Art of Linux Ricing (coming soon)  Simple Solution to Piracy; Custom File Formats and Blockchain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neocolonial Nyasaland</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/nyasaland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/nyasaland/</guid>
      <description>This is a Draft
 Poverty by Choice, a book by Donald Reuben Kamdonyo&amp;hellip;
Madando  Malawi sadzatheka Ambuye sanatisiye? Tiyambira pati? Khani ndi ndalama Ndikamaliza sukulu ndidzapanga chiyani? Anthu obwela akusokoneza zinthu Ufiti ndi kukhwima Kujoni kapena maiko ena? Magetsi akungo zima zima Ma units andithera Ndalama nchilombo Mitengo ilibe ntchito Kwacha inafooka Kodi chizungu chimativutabe? Adokodatala sakundifunira zabwino! Timangouzana sitimalemba Katangale ndi boma Umphawi sungandiletse kukhala ndi ana   Ngati sitisamala tikhala ngati abale athu aku Zambia&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thokozani; A Story about Gratitude</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/thokozani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/thokozani/</guid>
      <description>This is a draft
  God Family Internet Great Teachers Travel  God Family Internet Satoshi Nakamoto -
YouTube - real people, not actors
Udemy - High quality courses
Great Teachers TK Coleman - Dreams dont come true, decision do. It takes value creation to make money&amp;hellip;
Robert Kiyosaki - Financial education&amp;hellip; Gods money, peoples money and governments money
Jim Kwik - Knowledge is not power, its potential power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bye Bye Plutonomy, Welcome Freedom!</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/plutonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/plutonomy/</guid>
      <description>This is a draft
 Intro Darkness is the absence of light and to some literal degree, the abundance of melanin. The topic that&amp;rsquo;s going to be tackled in this essay is one regarding, Afropolitans, citizens of Africa. The essay will draw upon a documentary that piqued my interest on YouTube entitled, The shocking reason why black people are moving to Asia. No matter where we are geographically, we are still deeply rooted as a bigger picture of the African Diaspora.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended Definition 📚</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/xd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/xd/</guid>
      <description>The motto for Urban Dictionary is &amp;ldquo;Define Your World&amp;rdquo;, but thats probably offensive to Etymologists. Language is a living and breathing thing, its only natural that words change meaning over time, evolve or eventullay die out in usage. I find myself fascinated by words, not at the level of an etymologist or a sapiosexual, but at the polyglot level. I claim to have a deeper understanding of some words which i have interpreted using some twisted logic and this is a list of those words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afropolitan Excellence</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/exellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/exellence/</guid>
      <description>  This is a draft
 Emancipate yourself from mental slavery, none but ourselves can free our minds &amp;ndash; Bob Marley. Afropolitan excellence is an essay that aims to shed light in the darkness, give hope to the hopeless and promote the beauty of Afropolitanism.
Living Legends  Anime studio in Japan K-Beauty Product (South Korea) Stormzy Sam Okyere. Israel Adesanya Angee Floyd - Comedian in Vietnam MMA Artist in JP from Ghana Jason Gatewood (Journalist) - JP Han Hyunmin - Model  Western  Hip hop to Billionaire (Jay Z) Basketball to Entrepreneur (Michael Jordan) Prince EA Rudy Francisco TK Coleman   Historical  Nelson Mandela Martin Luther King Jr Bob Marley Malcolm X  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A ( ͡👁️ ͜ʖ ͡👁️)</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/qa/</guid>
      <description>Content is updating&amp;hellip;.
 Who is Prince Kaizen Namwali? A Neovim scribe with a Second Brain aspiring to be a Game Developer who happens to use Arch Linux.
 Whats the best way to contact PKN?
 His mode of communication comprises of eMail and Discord
 What is PKN&amp;rsquo;s go to tagline on the internet?
 Afropolitan Lifelong Learner, Digital Nomad &amp;amp; Game Developer
   🧠  Q&amp;A + Prince Kaizen Namwali  !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Death of Academia</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/academia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/academia/</guid>
      <description>College is not the only way&amp;hellip;
I had an epiphany when i came to the realization that college opt outs and drop outs have something in common&amp;hellip;.
 Self Taught Apprenticeship (mentor, real teachers, bootcamp&amp;hellip;) Internship (on the job training)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year: Second Brain 🧠</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/2021/</guid>
      <description>Everyone starts out the new year year with high hopes and expectations. They outline their so called resolutions which are a compass that will enable them to navigate through the year and make the most of it, but only a few succeed or completely abandon their routine. 2021 could have been just another year for me, but something was different or rather I had acquired something that would allow me to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description> Welcome to my Blog! My name is Prince Kaizen Namwali, an Afropolitan from the warm heart of Africa 🇲🇼. I am a Lifelong Learner, Digital Nomad &amp;amp; Game Dev.
 OS 💻: Artix Linux + AwesomeWM  Engine 🎮 : Godot Editor 🖥️: Neovim + Spacevim &amp;amp; Onivim 2 Langs ❤️: Go, GDScript, Lua, Bash Art 🔥: Inkscape, Gimp, Aseprite, DAW : Reaper Second Brain 🧠: Obsidian Foam &amp;amp; Markor Tech 🚀: Hugo, Browser 🌍: EinkBro, Privacy Browser &amp;amp;, Qutebrowser LibreWolf Wallet ₿: Metamask &amp;amp; Monero CLI Addons:: uBlock Origin, Dark Reader, IPFS Companion, Lighthouse, Leechblock NG, NoScript, uMatrix  Digital Footprint  Github  Audius Stackoverflow Discord Dribbble LMMS BitDegree Creary Game Jolt Itch Kitsu AniList 3Box Spring Role Satellite Publish0x Peepeth LBRY  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sayonara 2020 💔</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/2020/</guid>
      <description>Covid-19, a virus whose name shall never be forgotten. A virus that forced humans beings to connect and change. A virus synonymous with the words: change, catastrophe,fear, doubt, failure, shutdown, blame, cancellation and so much more. Many things can be said about the year 2020, and I truly believe everyone has a story to tell, no matter what human distinction is placed upon us. I wasnt spared from the effects of the pandemic, not even by a long shot,and this is my story&amp;hellip; For the first time in my life, i experienced what its like to have your plans not work out, as if that has never happened before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>