<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Second Brain</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Second Brain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2021 Prince Namwali</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mater Artium Necessitas 🚀</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/uvumbuzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/uvumbuzi/</guid>
      <description>Mater artium necessitas is a quote by Plato that was translated by a theologian by the name Benjamin Jowett, which means necessity is the mother of invention Throughout my encounter with this english proverb I have found that almost all instances of it have one thing in common. I would humbly extend the quote by saying necessity is the mother of invention, but it all starts with a question .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neocolonial Nyasaland</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/nyasaland/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/nyasaland/</guid>
      <description>This is a Draft
 Poverty by Choice, a book by Donald Reuben Kamdonyo&amp;hellip;
Madando  Malawi sadzatheka Ambuye sanatisiye? Tiyambira pati? Khani ndi ndalama Ndikamaliza sukulu ndidzapanga chiyani? Anthu obwela akusokoneza zinthu Ufiti ndi kukhwima Kujoni kapena maiko ena? Magetsi akungo zima zima Ma units andithera Ndalama nchilombo Mitengo ilibe ntchito Kwacha inafooka Kodi chizungu chimativutabe? Adokodatala sakundifunira zabwino! Timangouzana sitimalemba Katangale ndi boma Umphawi sungandiletse kukhala ndi ana   Ngati sitisamala tikhala ngati abale athu aku Zambia&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thokozani; A Story about Gratitude</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/thokozani/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/thokozani/</guid>
      <description>This is a draft
  God Family Internet Great Teachers Travel  God Family Internet Satoshi Nakamoto -
YouTube - real people, not actors
Udemy - High quality courses
Great Teachers TK Coleman - Dreams dont come true, decision do. It takes value creation to make money&amp;hellip;
Robert Kiyosaki - Financial education&amp;hellip; Gods money, peoples money and governments money
Jim Kwik - Knowledge is not power, its potential power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bye Bye Plutonomy, Welcome Freedom!</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/plutonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/plutonomy/</guid>
      <description>This is a draft
 Intro Darkness is the absence of light and to some literal degree, the abundance of melanin. The topic that&amp;rsquo;s going to be tackled in this essay is one regarding, Afropolitans, citizens of Africa. The essay will draw upon a documentary that piqued my interest on YouTube entitled, The shocking reason why black people are moving to Asia. No matter where we are geographically, we are still deeply rooted as a bigger picture of the African Diaspora.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended Definition 📚</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/xd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/xd/</guid>
      <description>The motto for Urban Dictionary is &amp;ldquo;Define Your World&amp;rdquo;, but thats probably offensive to Etymologists. Language is a living and breathing thing, its only natural that words change meaning over time, evolve or eventullay die out in usage. I find myself fascinated by words, not at the level of an etymologist or a sapiosexual, but at the polyglot level. I claim to have a deeper understanding of some words which i have interpreted using some twisted logic and this is a list of those words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afropolitan Excellence</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/exellence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/exellence/</guid>
      <description>  This is a draft
 Emancipate yourself from mental slavery, none but ourselves can free our minds &amp;ndash; Bob Marley. Afropolitan excellence is an essay that aims to shed light in the darkness, give hope to the hopeless and promote the beauty of Afropolitanism.
Living Legends  Anime studio in Japan K-Beauty Product (South Korea) Stormzy Sam Okyere. Israel Adesanya Angee Floyd - Comedian in Vietnam MMA Artist in JP from Ghana Jason Gatewood (Journalist) - JP Han Hyunmin - Model  Western  Hip hop to Billionaire (Jay Z) Basketball to Entrepreneur (Michael Jordan) Prince EA Rudy Francisco TK Coleman   Historical  Nelson Mandela Martin Luther King Jr Bob Marley Malcolm X  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A ( ͡👁️ ͜ʖ ͡👁️)</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/qa/</guid>
      <description>Content is updating&amp;hellip;.
 Who is Prince Kaizen Namwali? A Neovim scribe with a Second Brain aspiring to be a Game Developer who happens to use Arch Linux.
 Whats the best way to contact PKN?
 His mode of communication comprises of eMail and Discord
 What is PKN&amp;rsquo;s go to tagline on the internet?
 Afropolitan Lifelong Learner, Digital Nomad &amp;amp; Game Developer
   🧠  Q&amp;A + Prince Kaizen Namwali  !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Death of Academia</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/academia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/academia/</guid>
      <description>College is not the only way&amp;hellip;
I had an epiphany when i came to the realization that college opt outs and drop outs have something in common&amp;hellip;.
 Self Taught Apprenticeship (mentor, real teachers, bootcamp&amp;hellip;) Internship (on the job training)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year: Second Brain 🧠</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/2021/</guid>
      <description>Everyone starts out the new year year with high hopes and expectations. They outline their so called resolutions which are a compass that will enable them to navigate through the year and make the most of it, but only a few succeed or completely abandon their routine. 2021 could have been just another year for me, but something was different or rather I had acquired something that would allow me to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sayonara 2020 💔</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/post/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/post/2020/</guid>
      <description>Covid-19, a virus whose name shall never be forgotten. A virus that forced humans beings to connect and change. A virus synonymous with the words: change, catastrophe,fear, doubt, failure, shutdown, blame, cancellation and so much more. Many things can be said about the year 2020, and I truly believe everyone has a story to tell, no matter what human distinction is placed upon us. I wasnt spared from the effects of the pandemic, not even by a long shot,and this is my story&amp;hellip; For the first time in my life, i experienced what its like to have your plans not work out, as if that has never happened before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>