<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Prince Namwali</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Prince Namwali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dreams &amp; Brainwaves</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dreams/</guid>
      <description>Dreams will always be dreams, nothing less and nothing more
Dreaming about sandwiches never filled anyone’s stomach
The choice to go to a restaurant or grocery store filled thy stomach
With the proper ingredients a meal was guaranteed
For the right price thyself could feed
Dreams will always be dreams, nothing more and nothing less
What exactly is a dream?
A special brainwave reading called Theta
A state associated with creativity, insight and reduced consciousness</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflammatory Questions</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/inflammatory-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/inflammatory-questions/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of burning questions that i have come to find answers to by reading various books, listening to podcasts and scouring the web. These questions arose because i felt that school only caused this post traumatic growth disorder. School only taught and continues to teach what the government wants you to know. Luckily enough, schools are not the gatekeepers of information. This post points you towards those resources, while giving a brief overview, not complete answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layers of the Web</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/web-layers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/web-layers/</guid>
      <description>Relearning The Internet Today i decided to relearn about the internet. As a casual surfer, i thought i knew all that there is to know about the internet, but that wasn&amp;rsquo;t the case. I just believed the internet was just this magical place people went to, in order to do all sorts of things like shopping, streaming videos, reading manhwa and what have you, but there is more. The layer of the internet that i have spent most of time on is something called the surface web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artix Linux Installation</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/artix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/artix/</guid>
      <description>Why? Not long ago, my knowledge of operating systems was limited. I only thought that Windows and MacOS were the only operating systems in existence,but little did i know that there was another universe out there. A universe packed with real freedom,better security, extreme customizability, faster and filled with an even larger community, than my brain could ever comprehend. I remember the feeling of excitement that ran across my face, when i first installed a linux distribution on my personal computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>365 Spreadsheet Challenge</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/spreadsheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/spreadsheet/</guid>
      <description>Notes What i learned from using spreadsheets every day for a single year
 You cant change what you dont measure We consume more than we create If you want to make a change in your life, you have to do the opposite. Create more than you consume.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Brain, Left Behind</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/brain-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/brain-health/</guid>
      <description>Super Psyche A cross platform gamified brain heatlh application that helps people learn faster and achieve more.
ETA *2025</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friendly Documentation</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/documentation/</guid>
      <description>Notes Documentation is the best friend of a developer.
Shocking realization: you dont have to memorize everything. You can always reference it. Documentation, like books are not a one time thing. They are a friend that you can always go back to every single time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procgen Music</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/procgen_music/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/procgen_music/</guid>
      <description>Procedural generation aka Procgen&amp;hellip;.
Notes Audio Samples  Ujo Music LMMS Projects Soundcloud  Ujo music link, my soundcloud link, lmms link
  using lmms
  using soundtrap
  Making the final switch to reaper
  Most recent sample (9 second preview)
  Is knowing solfege relevant?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Homelessness</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/digital-homelessness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/digital-homelessness/</guid>
      <description>Notes Its one of the most widespread problems that affects internet users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automation &amp; Laziness</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/automated-laziness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/automated-laziness/</guid>
      <description>Notes The ship cover resembles the nature of the hydro mode of transportaion, automated.
Challenges  Create a shell script or tasker script that automatically erases metadata for every photo captured using phones camera   The script would need to have access to the DCIM folder. The script would cd (change directory) The script would need to initiate an application that is specifically designed to erase metadata Here is the real challenge: Whats required?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living Gapps Free</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/gapss-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/gapss-free/</guid>
      <description>What Are Gapps? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lingua Franca</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/lingua-franca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/lingua-franca/</guid>
      <description>Notes  Neuro Linguistic Programming Bash Scripiting Go  Fun Fact:
 Markup languaes (markdown, toml, html&amp;hellip;) Scripting languages (Lua, bash, fish, zsh &amp;hellip;) Programming languges (Go, Dart, Python)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is College The Only Way?</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/college/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/college/</guid>
      <description>Is College The Only Way? The simple answer is no, but lets dive deeper into why?
Select Few Opt Out Drop Out Technical Answer Sometimes people will only believe something if presented the data. The challenge is to write a web scraping programming that finds information about different career choices. The program will be programmed in two ways. The first being, that it only find the career choices that dont require a degree with real stories to back the claim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unstable Productivity</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/unstablee-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/unstablee-productivity/</guid>
      <description>I am a maverick when it comes to my software selection choice. I like to be on the bleeding edge of technology, i am never satisfied in being like everyone else that uses stable builds of an application. I like to have a taste a of the feature, bugs be damned, it wont stop me from witnessing the birth of new ideas and experiences that can only be lived by using unstable builds of software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jah Patriarch</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/jah_patriarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/jah_patriarch/</guid>
      <description>Government is the stronghold, all must obey
The laws are flimsy, there is room to play
Lets make prostitution legal, the verdict - strip clubs
Lets make speeding legal, the verdict - car races
Lets makes stealing legal, the verdict - ethical hacking and surveillance capitalism
Lets make fighting legal, the verdict MMA sports
Lets make killing legal, the verdict - army, armed police &amp;amp; death penalty
Lets make tax evasion legal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Facts v3.0 </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/globalfacts3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/globalfacts3/</guid>
      <description>If you read something and don’t apply it
You are no different than someone who is illiterate
If you watch a video and dont apply it
You are no different than someone who is blind
If you listen to a podcast and dont apply it
You are no different than someone who is deaf
You cant consume your way to a better life, you have to create it
Consumption is passive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanashi Dearu Koto</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/nanashi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/nanashi/</guid>
      <description>Generation Z is my suffix
Born to swipe and masters of the art of remix
A generation of lifelong learners and digital nomads
Surfing the web in search of knowledge
Drowning in Dapps in search for value
Escaping reality in search of meaning
Building the next big thing, instead of dreaming
A few syllables to trigger my assistants, OK Google, Alexa and maybe Siri
Instant clicks of gratification. So much information, like what in tarnation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 25: Loci/ Memory Palace</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/loci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/loci/</guid>
      <description>Loci aka memory palace
Location&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 24: Feynman Technique</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/feynman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/feynman/</guid>
      <description>Ultimately its about teaching what you learn to others. Its an active way of learning vs passive learning (taught in schools, just consume information like robots)
 Choose a concept you are interested in learning   The keyword is *interest , without it anything you learn wont stick  Teach it to someone else   I dont know the true source of the quote, but it reads &amp;ldquo;if you cant explain it a 6 year old, you dont understand it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 23: Rational Emotive Behavior Therapy</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/rebt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/rebt/</guid>
      <description>The most beautiful thing i ever learned as far as Brain Health goes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 22: Neuro-Linguistic Programming</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/n-lp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/n-lp/</guid>
      <description>Its not exactly a mental model, but something relevant to understanding your Brain in great detail. #Neuroscience &amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 21: Arbitrage</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/arbitrage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/arbitrage/</guid>
      <description>I like to think of the term Geoarbitrage as coined by Tim Ferris. Its all about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 20: Feedback Loop</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Its a system&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 19: Eisenhower Matrix</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/eisenhower/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/eisenhower/</guid>
      <description>Named after one of the previous USA presidents</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 18: Ikigai</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/ikigai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/ikigai/</guid>
      <description>Japanese mental model</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 17: Circle of Competence</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/circle/</guid>
      <description>Attributed to Warren Buffet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 16: Thought Field Therapy</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/tft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/tft/</guid>
      <description>Quite similar to the visualizaion mental model</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 15: Emotion Freedom Technique</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/eft/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/eft/</guid>
      <description>Emotion Freedom Technique (EFT) aka Mudra aka Jigam aka Tapping</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 14: Supply &amp; Demand</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/supply/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/supply/</guid>
      <description>Its the one mental model that transcended beyond economics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 13: Reverse Thinking</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/reverse/</guid>
      <description>A great example that i like to associate with this mental model is with the question of what do you want to do when you grow up.
I like to picture someone who answered with the response, Doctor. Why?
 Make money, the #1 response  With reverse thinking its about thinking of the end in mind. A better answer to the follow up question of why would be:
 Find a cure for X disease Make healthcare knowledge more accessible   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 12: BRIGHT MINDS</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/minds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/minds/</guid>
      <description>Attributed to Dr Daniel Amen in his literary publication entitled Memory Rescue</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 11: Compounding</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/compouding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/compouding/</guid>
      <description>This is where the 10X Rule falls into place. Its mathematical
 Compound interest  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 10: Law of 33%</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/33/</guid>
      <description>This mental model is more about relationships (Tai Lopez got it from some source&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 09: Visualization</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/visualization/</guid>
      <description>Visualization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 08: Bucket List</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/pareto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/pareto/</guid>
      <description>80/20 Rule</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 07: Regret Minimzation</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/regret/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/regret/</guid>
      <description>This mental model asks the question will i regret not doing this in X years? If the answer is yes, go ahead and do the thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 06: Gamification</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/gamification/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/gamification/</guid>
      <description>Gaming isnt just a past time, there is more to it&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 05: Zettelkasten</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/zettelkasten/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/zettelkasten/</guid>
      <description>Its a German word&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 04: Bucket List</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/bucketlist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/bucketlist/</guid>
      <description>This mental models asks the question, what do you want to do before you die?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 03: Mind Map</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/mindmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/mindmap/</guid>
      <description>This mental model/ framework is attributed to Tony Buzan
Super asweom mental model even if you arent creative. The most amazing thing i discovered with this model is that it can help me summarize a book without even reading it. You need NLP for it to work. You just have to look at the table of contents only, if the TOC is vague you can quickly speed read the chapters and get an overall theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 02: Second Brain</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/second_brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/second_brain/</guid>
      <description>BASB (Building A Second Brain) Super awesome mental model i just learned this year by Tiago Forte.
PARA - Projects, Areas, Resources and Archive
 Projects - Specific goal with a dealine Areas - Continuous improvement Resources - Content consumpton - books, podcasts, videos Archive - No longer useful (deleted)  Projects have metaplan that outline the questions: who, what, when and why?
 Break big projects into smaller ones (Kaizen) and also create metaplans for those as well  The notes should be personal, not aimed at public presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Resolutions</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/new_year/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/new_year/</guid>
      <description>Goals  Learning out loud Learn how to create ebooks using Markdown and Pandoc Build a website using Hugo Create a website on IPFS Fully adopt the Crash mindset Learn &amp;amp; Master Vim Create a name generator Take more cold showers Learn Korean - Read Manhwa without waiting for scanlators Create an effective Second Brain Daily Blogging (Work in progress&amp;hellip;) Hack sleep for lucid dreaming Buy a custom domain (.xyz migrated from the netlify subdomain) Improve my touch typing (160WPM).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Model 01: Kaizen</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/kaizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/kaizen/</guid>
      <description>Kaizen asks the question, what small steps can i take to improve or change X?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 Year In Review</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/year_in_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/year_in_review/</guid>
      <description>What I Learned  Inter-Planetary File System (IPFS) Blockstack Privacy Hardening using Privacy Tools Markdown Decentralized Applications (Dapps) Metamask Reedsy Figma Unstoppable Domains Search Engine Optimization (SEO) - First page results on Google &amp;amp; other search engines (name search).   Content I Consumed  The Social Dilemna (Documentary) College is Dead Capitalism: A Love Story (Documentary) Minimalism: A Documentary About The Important Things The Stories We Tell About Money Dreams Dont Come True, Decisions Do Watch This Before You &amp;hellip; Bucket List Deconsructed Racism #BlackLivesMatter I Sued The School System Why I Hate School,But Love Education   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 Lessons</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/covid-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/covid-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Covid-19 2020 shall be recalled in history books as the year of change. Multiple things happened, many words can be assigned to the year 2020, but it all comes down to one final world, change. 2020 was supposed to be the year of vision, as a reference to visual acuity, something utilized in the medical/healthcare field.
Lessons  Health is the greatest wealth Financial Freedom is better than financial security When a person is unable to change their situation, they are forced to change themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Success</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/decentralized_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/decentralized_success/</guid>
      <description>Unstoppable, private and transparent are your properties
Solidity is a drug that will free the world from the atrocities
From centralization, data monetization and inflation
Tax evaders, pros, newbies and freedom seekers are welcome
Heaven on Earth is decentralized, for the male and female
Escape the fiat and become a whale
Living in the past is no different than being in jail
Smart contracts are the future and they will prevail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Stratum</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/cyber_stratum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/cyber_stratum/</guid>
      <description>We kill trees but our storage is digital
The topic of our tropical planet is hysterical
Man made machines and machines make man money
When the sea level and temperature is rising, ain’t that funny or is it surprising?
This is the raid, charade, masquerade and parade of the greenhouse gases
Millennial’s shall suffer if we don’t fight these old timers and old dumb asses
The old timers near death, why would they care?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited Shoutouts</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/shoutout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/shoutout/</guid>
      <description>Shoutout to Covid-19
For granting us the time to go after our dreams
Shoutout to YouTube
For all the clickbait, entertaining and informative videos
Shoutout to memes
For adding humor to ordinary images
Shoutout to Crash.co
For providing people with a better signal than resume or cover letter
Shoutout to Udemy
For the countless affordable courses and ability to connect with instructors
Shoutout to Bitcoin
For making people question, what is money really?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Room Full of Dead Dreams</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dead-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dead-dreams/</guid>
      <description>I am sitting in a room.
Full of silence, its called a classroom
A room full of doubt and dead dreams
Screaming, why am i here?
Please let me out!
Shouting, do grades really matter?
Please let me out!
Crying, is this the only way?
Please let me out!
Sobbing, why does time move so slow?
Please let me out!
Mumbling, why does school even exist?
Please let me out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sudo&#39;s Requiem</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/sudos_requiem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/sudos_requiem/</guid>
      <description>Water maketh man whole, but action maketh man complete
A man is an island and a woman is a continent
Through acts of human love making a child is born
The blank slate of Tabula Rasa and an imprint period left to develop
A birth of cognitive distortions and rejuvenation of mental models
An epiphany of REBT and ascension of humanity
The limitations of proverbs and psalms, the abandonment of philosophy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anno Denomini</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/anno-denomini/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/anno-denomini/</guid>
      <description>Anno Denomini, the year of our lord.
The lord of artificial intelligence, the challenger of divine beings and God.
Anno Denomini, the year of our master.
The one who transcended natural language processing and created an artificial disaster.
Anno Denomini, the year of our species.
The time when the robot population exceeded that of humans and other.
Anno Denomini, the year of the break.
When internet of things became integrated into all living and non living things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bye.Bye Plutonomy. Welcome Freedom </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/bye-plutonomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/bye-plutonomy/</guid>
      <description>This publication is an analysis of this video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Wu to World</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/wu_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/wu_world/</guid>
      <description>Words replace thoughts and thoughts replace action
A healthcare official getting sick is the definition of irony
Wash your hands you mortal beings and lean not on your old ways
The air is contagious, cover thy face and cover thy lungs
Covid-19 has only just begun, beware of fake news
Stress not over the things that you have not control
Doctors are not immortal
Celebrities are not gods
You might eventually get it, but what are the odds?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hoarder&#39;s Legacy</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/hoarder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/hoarder/</guid>
      <description>The hoarders legacy is too much to bare
Too much stuff and junk piled up everywhere
Moderation is an offensive word and minimalism is something they have never heard
They are convinced that contentment is only a few purchases away
Don’t touch my stuff and stay away
Lost within materialism they never feel enough
When disaster strikes they learn to let go because its just stuff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Facts v2.0</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/global_facts2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/global_facts2/</guid>
      <description>Life is difficult and that is a fact
Change happens one day at a time and that’s that
Life is difficult and that is a fact
We think and then we feel, that’s that
Life is difficult and that is a fact
The past is gone, the future will come, we live in the present and we must utilize it
before it becomes past
Life is difficult and that is a fact</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Whom Shall I Blame?</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/scapegoat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/scapegoat/</guid>
      <description>The job search is fierce and fiercely it is
3000 applications and only 12 take the bait
I wish you were fuel efficient and truly roadworthy
Your mileage and health, force me to breath in insoluble doubt
Recruiters are distant relatives, they are too far to reach
Recruiters are wild animals, somewhere on the beach
Where do you see yourself 5 years from now?
In a land far, far away</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Long Does It Take To Learn Programming?</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/programming_duration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/programming_duration/</guid>
      <description>Notes   I believe the answer depends on the environment&amp;hellip;.
  If it takes 1 year, its because you are using MacOS or Windows, i dont see why it would take long on Linux, especially Arch or an Arch based distro
  Or just about anything that has a steep learning curve like gentoo, openBSD &amp;hellip;
  Thats my take, lets look at what other say, but lets analyze their words using neuro linguistic programming to get a better picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Afropolitan Ambassador</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/afropolitan-ambassador/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/afropolitan-ambassador/</guid>
      <description>2020 has been a crazy year&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
