<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Prince Namwali</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Prince Namwali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Q&amp;A ( ͡👁️ ͜ʖ ͡👁️)</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/qa/</guid>
      <description>Content is updating&amp;hellip;.
 Who is Prince Kaizen Namwali?   A Neovim scribe with a Second Brain aspiring to be a Game Developer who happens to use Arch Linux.  Whats the best way to contact PKN?   His mode of communication comprises of eMail and Discord  What is PKN&amp;rsquo;s go to tagline on the internet?   Afropolitan Lifelong Learner, Digital Nomad &amp;amp; Game Developer      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extended Definition 📚</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/extended_definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/extended_definition/</guid>
      <description>The motto for Urban Dictionary is &amp;ldquo;Define Your World&amp;rdquo;, but thats probably offensive to Etymologists. Language is a living and breathing thing, its only natural that words change meaning over time, evolve or eventullay die out in usage. I find myself fascinated by words, not at the level of an etymologist or a sapiosexual, but at the polyglot level. I claim to have a deeper understanding of some words which i have interpreted using some twisted logic and this is a list of those words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mater Artium Necessitas 🚀</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/uvumbuzi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/uvumbuzi/</guid>
      <description>Mater artium necessitas is a quote by Plato that was translated by a theologian by the name Benjamin Jowett, which means necessity is the mother of invention Throughout my encounter with this english proverb I have found that almost all instances of it have one thing in common. I would humbly extend the quote by saying necessity is the mother of invention, but it all starts with a question . Necessity is the behind the reason that has led to all the human inventions recorded throughout history and the ongoing innovation that take place today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year: Second Brain 🧠</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2021-reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2021-reboot/</guid>
      <description>Everyone starts out the new year year with high hopes and expectations. They outline their so called resolutions which are a compass that will enable them to navigate through the year and make the most of it, but only a few succeed or completely abandon their routine. 2021 could have been just another year for me, but something was different or rather I had acquired something that would allow me to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sayonara 2020 💔</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/2020/</guid>
      <description>Covid-19, a virus whose name shall never be forgotten. A virus that forced humans beings to connect and change. A virus synonymous with the words: change, catastrophe,fear, doubt, failure, shutdown, blame, cancellation and so much more. Many things can be said about the year 2020, and I truly believe everyone has a story to tell, no matter what human distinction is placed upon us. I wasnt spared from the effects of the pandemic, not even by a long shot,and this is my story&amp;hellip; For the first time in my life, i experienced what its like to have your plans not work out, as if that has never happened before.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
