<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poems on Prince Namwali</title>
    <link>https://33nano.xyz/categories/poems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Poems on Prince Namwali</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://33nano.xyz/categories/poems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dreams &amp; Brainwaves</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dreams/</guid>
      <description>Dreams will always be dreams, nothing less and nothing more
Dreaming about sandwiches never filled anyone’s stomach
The choice to go to a restaurant or grocery store filled thy stomach
With the proper ingredients a meal was guaranteed
For the right price thyself could feed
Dreams will always be dreams, nothing more and nothing less
What exactly is a dream?
A special brainwave reading called Theta
A state associated with creativity, insight and reduced consciousness</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jah Patriarch</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/jah_patriarch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/jah_patriarch/</guid>
      <description>Government is the stronghold, all must obey
The laws are flimsy, there is room to play
Lets make prostitution legal, the verdict - strip clubs
Lets make speeding legal, the verdict - car races
Lets makes stealing legal, the verdict - ethical hacking and surveillance capitalism
Lets make fighting legal, the verdict MMA sports
Lets make killing legal, the verdict - army, armed police &amp;amp; death penalty
Lets make tax evasion legal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Facts v3.0 </title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/globalfacts3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/globalfacts3/</guid>
      <description>If you read something and don’t apply it
You are no different than someone who is illiterate
If you watch a video and dont apply it
You are no different than someone who is blind
If you listen to a podcast and dont apply it
You are no different than someone who is deaf
You cant consume your way to a better life, you have to create it
Consumption is passive</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanashi Dearu Koto</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/nanashi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/nanashi/</guid>
      <description>Generation Z is my suffix
Born to swipe and masters of the art of remix
A generation of lifelong learners and digital nomads
Surfing the web in search of knowledge
Drowning in Dapps in search for value
Escaping reality in search of meaning
Building the next big thing, instead of dreaming
A few syllables to trigger my assistants, OK Google, Alexa and maybe Siri
Instant clicks of gratification. So much information, like what in tarnation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Success</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/decentralized_success/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/decentralized_success/</guid>
      <description>Unstoppable, private and transparent are your properties
Solidity is a drug that will free the world from the atrocities
From centralization, data monetization and inflation
Tax evaders, pros, newbies and freedom seekers are welcome
Heaven on Earth is decentralized, for the male and female
Escape the fiat and become a whale
Living in the past is no different than being in jail
Smart contracts are the future and they will prevail</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Stratum</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/cyber_stratum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/cyber_stratum/</guid>
      <description>We kill trees but our storage is digital
The topic of our tropical planet is hysterical
Man made machines and machines make man money
When the sea level and temperature is rising, ain’t that funny or is it surprising?
This is the raid, charade, masquerade and parade of the greenhouse gases
Millennial’s shall suffer if we don’t fight these old timers and old dumb asses
The old timers near death, why would they care?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited Shoutouts</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/shoutout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/shoutout/</guid>
      <description>Shoutout to Covid-19
For granting us the time to go after our dreams
Shoutout to YouTube
For all the clickbait, entertaining and informative videos
Shoutout to memes
For adding humor to ordinary images
Shoutout to Crash.co
For providing people with a better signal than resume or cover letter
Shoutout to Udemy
For the countless affordable courses and ability to connect with instructors
Shoutout to Bitcoin
For making people question, what is money really?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Room Full of Dead Dreams</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dead-dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/dead-dreams/</guid>
      <description>I am sitting in a room.
Full of silence, its called a classroom
A room full of doubt and dead dreams
Screaming, why am i here?
Please let me out!
Shouting, do grades really matter?
Please let me out!
Crying, is this the only way?
Please let me out!
Sobbing, why does time move so slow?
Please let me out!
Mumbling, why does school even exist?
Please let me out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sudo&#39;s Requiem</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/sudos_requiem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/sudos_requiem/</guid>
      <description>Water maketh man whole, but action maketh man complete
A man is an island and a woman is a continent
Through acts of human love making a child is born
The blank slate of Tabula Rasa and an imprint period left to develop
A birth of cognitive distortions and rejuvenation of mental models
An epiphany of REBT and ascension of humanity
The limitations of proverbs and psalms, the abandonment of philosophy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anno Denomini</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/anno-denomini/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/anno-denomini/</guid>
      <description>Anno Denomini, the year of our lord.
The lord of artificial intelligence, the challenger of divine beings and God.
Anno Denomini, the year of our master.
The one who transcended natural language processing and created an artificial disaster.
Anno Denomini, the year of our species.
The time when the robot population exceeded that of humans and other.
Anno Denomini, the year of the break.
When internet of things became integrated into all living and non living things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Wu to World</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/wu_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/wu_world/</guid>
      <description>Words replace thoughts and thoughts replace action
A healthcare official getting sick is the definition of irony
Wash your hands you mortal beings and lean not on your old ways
The air is contagious, cover thy face and cover thy lungs
Covid-19 has only just begun, beware of fake news
Stress not over the things that you have not control
Doctors are not immortal
Celebrities are not gods
You might eventually get it, but what are the odds?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Hoarder&#39;s Legacy</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/hoarder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/hoarder/</guid>
      <description>The hoarders legacy is too much to bare
Too much stuff and junk piled up everywhere
Moderation is an offensive word and minimalism is something they have never heard
They are convinced that contentment is only a few purchases away
Don’t touch my stuff and stay away
Lost within materialism they never feel enough
When disaster strikes they learn to let go because its just stuff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Facts v2.0</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/global_facts2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/global_facts2/</guid>
      <description>Life is difficult and that is a fact
Change happens one day at a time and that’s that
Life is difficult and that is a fact
We think and then we feel, that’s that
Life is difficult and that is a fact
The past is gone, the future will come, we live in the present and we must utilize it
before it becomes past
Life is difficult and that is a fact</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Whom Shall I Blame?</title>
      <link>https://33nano.xyz/blog/scapegoat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://33nano.xyz/blog/scapegoat/</guid>
      <description>The job search is fierce and fiercely it is
3000 applications and only 12 take the bait
I wish you were fuel efficient and truly roadworthy
Your mileage and health, force me to breath in insoluble doubt
Recruiters are distant relatives, they are too far to reach
Recruiters are wild animals, somewhere on the beach
Where do you see yourself 5 years from now?
In a land far, far away</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
